temple os an open source 64-bit operating system designed to be the
Temple os 一个开源的 64 位操作系统，旨在成为
third temple prophesized by the bible it was created in 2005 by terry davis an
圣经预言的第三座神殿。它是由特里戴维斯于 2005 年创建的，他是一位
exceptionally talented programmer diagnosed with schizophrenia he wrote
才华横溢的程序员，被诊断患有精神分裂症，他
the entire operating system himself at his parents house in las vegas which
自己在拉斯维加斯的父母家中编写了整个操作系统。
included a bootloader kernel window manager 3d graphics library and multiple
包括一个引导加载程序内核窗口管理器 3d 图形库和多个
games all powered by his own compiler and custom programming language called
游戏，所有这些都由他自己的编译器和称为
holy c amazingly it all fits in under 100 000 lines of code at 1.4 megabytes
神圣 c 的自定义
just as god intended he believed he was god's chosen programmer and implemented
编程语言提供支持 并实现
features described as a modern day way of speaking in tongues it renders
了被描述为现代语言方式的功能 它
graphics at 640x480 resolution limited to only 16 colors the underlying
以 640x480 的分辨率渲染图形，仅限于 16 种颜色 基础
language holy c resembles c or c plus plus but has functions that can be
语言 圣 c 类似于 c 或 c plusplus，但具有可以在
invoked without parentheses or arguments and uses just in time compilation which
没有括号或参数的情况下调用的函数，并且仅用于 时间编译，这
means it doubles as a shell language that can be executed directly from the
意味着它可以兼作一种可以直接执行的 shell 语言 m
terminal unlike other operating systems like linux or windows it's ring zero
终端与 linux 或 windows 等其他操作系统不同，它仅为零环
only which means everything happens directly in the kernel including user
，这意味着一切都直接发生在内核中，包括用户
programs you have complete control over the operating system source code and
程序，您可以完全控制操作系统源代码和
hardware that may not seem very safe but it's the way it is because it's fun to
硬件，这可能看起来不是很安全，但它就是这样 因为上手很有趣，所以
get started you'll first want to download the iso file from the temple os
您首先要从 Temple os 网站下载 iso 文件，然后
website from there use a tool like virtualbox configured for a 64-bit
使用为 64 位操作系统配置的 virtualbox 之类的工具
operating system that boots this file on startup it creates a single immortal
，在启动时启动该文件，它会创建一个
task named adam it's the father of every other task just like in the book of
名为 adam 的不朽任务 它是所有其他任务之父，就像在
genesis it can also take advantage of multiple cpu cores where each core gets
创世记中一样，它还可以利用多个 cpu 核心，每个核心一旦进入其中，就会获得
its own immortal set task once inside you can take the tour or immediately
自己的不朽设置任务，您可以进行游览或
start speaking in tongues by hitting f7 which generates a pseudo-random word
通过按 f7 立即开始说方言，生成 一个来自上帝的伪随机词
from god you can also have god draw you a picture with shift f6 to perform a god
你也可以让上帝用 shift f6 给你画一张照片来执行一个
doodle that was fun but now use ctrl m to open up the personal menu from here
有趣但现在使用 ctrlm 打开的上帝涂鸦 从这里的个人菜单
you'll find a huge variety of games like 3d first person shooters 2d strategy
你会发现各种各样的游戏，比如3d 第一人称射击游戏 2d 战略
games and simulations like after egypt where you play the role of moses and
游戏和模拟游戏，比如在埃及之后你扮演摩西的角色，
also has utilities to manage your finances and make music remember this is
还有实用程序来管理你的财务和制作音乐，记住这
all made possible by a custom graphics library if you're not happy with the way
一切都是制作的如果您对它的工作方式不满意，可以通过自定义图形库进行操作，
it works simply open up the source code make some modifications and holy c
只需打开源代码进行一些修改，然后神圣的 c
reboot and enjoy every line of code is right at your fingertips thanks to the
重新启动并享受每一行代码都在您的指尖，这要归功于
red sea file system the end result is one of the most complex pieces of
红海文件系统结束 结果是
software ever written by a solo developer but there's a lot more to this
由一个单独的开发人员编写的最复杂的软件之一，但这个故事还有更多内容
story and sadly terry davis passed away in 2018 at the age of 48. he was both a
，可悲的是，特里戴维斯于 2018 年去世，享年 48 岁。他既是一位
highly controversial internet personality and genius programmer this
极具争议的互联网名人，也是一位天才程序员。
has been temple os in 100 seconds hit the like button if you want to see more
100 秒内已经是 Templeos 如果你想看更多
weird videos like this thanks for watching and i will see you in the next
像这样的奇怪视频，请按赞按钮，谢谢观看，我会在下一个看到你
one